[English subtitles are available.]
I'm going to cook.
Let's get started.
Wow, there are so many dishes.
And they all look delicious.
They look so delicious.
I don't think
there can be any other food more
delicious than this.
Looking at the dinner, I can't believe
it's cooked by one person
in an entire afternoon.
Every day when I'm about to cook,
I will be thinking it as
staging a show.
You know what I mean?
Keep things organized.
You need to keep things organized.
Then I will be thinking
what I need to do
after this.
I enjoy designing the dishes,
such as meat dishes and vegetable dishes.
I think it's fun.
Everywhere we've been to,
we have unlocked new skills.
But as for Mr. Huang, it's different kitchens.
It's cooking.
Zhang Yixing.
I'm sorry, Master.
It's not working.
Neither does this one.
I had a pickle and
it was so salty that my head hurt.
I'm sorry, Master.
No problem.
That's what you need to go through
when you learn how to cook.
Master,
what's your secret for
cooking such delicious meals?
I cook for my good friends.
That motivates me to make good meals.
Let's make a toast for Mr. Huang.
Thank you, Mr. Huang.
May us enjoy great health.
For Mr. Huang.
Thank you, Mr. Huang.
Thank you, Mr. Huang, for the dinner.
You see we all use bowls.
Why do you use a cup?
I'm not hungry.
I'm happy
when I see you eating.
I'm planning to eat his food
for the rest of my life.
That's wishful thinking.
Do you think
one day
you won't like cooking?
I think you will always like the things
you truly love.
Jiong, I have to go to vomit.
What's wrong?
I need some rest.
I don't feel very well.
Go and take a break.
I feel really bad.
You don't need to cook today.
♪The little bird is leading the way.♪
♪The wind is breezing towards our face.♪
Mr. Huang.
I really think
you are like
providing us with
hotel service.
That's a very top comment.
The makeup artist asked me
if I need to get changed.
I told her that this is not pyjamas.
It's an exotic outfit.
It's also like the clothes you wear in spa.
Spa ropes.
Yes.
You look like the assistant
who gives customers access bracelets.
Yes.
Sir, No. 32 for you.
I want to make cinnamon rolls.
I want to find something to do.
We can work as a team.
Pour it in.
Use the milk to
mix the yeast.
That's enough.
I used to teach my daughter Duo Duo
to make the dough.
She really enjoyed it.
She likes using butter and flour
and bashing this thing.
Kids love this sort of thing.
They see it as a game.
It smells so good.
I can smell it from here.
Right? Smells great.
Look baby.
Baby.
Cute little baby.
Okay.
Okay, baby.
Yesterday
when we went to bed,
he got up and had a meeting.
He had a meeting...
I think I heard him having a meeting
in the other room.
He wasn't in a good mood.
He was stamping
in the bathroom.
Morning, Mr. He.
Morning.
My trainer is here.
I need to get ready for my concert.
I need to work out
to improve my performance.
Sure.
I'm just telling you.
Aren't you going to have some food first?
Are you going to work out with empty stomach?
Yes.
Working out with empty stomach?
Seems so.
Well,
he can at least eat an egg.
I can boil an egg for you.
Zhang Yixing.
Master.
I can boil an egg for you.
Don't worry.
Working out with an empty stomach
isn't really good.
I will be fine.
I will do some exercise before having breakfast.
Okay.
You can drink some milk.
At least eat something.
You need to eat something.
So stubborn.
He is so stubborn.
I want to ask his trainer
if he thinks it's good to
do exercise with an empty stomach.
I will ask him.
Are you going to ask?
I will go and ask.
Let's go.
Let's go and ask.
I'm curious to know too.
Morning.
Handsome Peng.
Peng also gets up.
You are the trainer, right?
Yes.
Hello.
This is my Master.
Mr. He.
Thank you.
Professional trainer.
Boxer.
Yes.
I'm an amateur.
Let's have a fight.
I don't fight.
I want to ask you a question.
Take him as an example.
He hasn't had breakfast
and he is wearing a knitted hat
to do exercise.
Is it good for him?
Aerobics with an empty stomach
can lose muscles.
It can lose muscles, right?
Yes.
But if his stomach has always been quite fragile,
is it bad for him?
You can't always work out
with an empty stomach, right?
It's best to have some to eat,
right?
Yes.
Okay. Carry on.
Keep going!
Thank you.
I'm just here to check him out.
You'd better eat before workout.
Okay?
Okay.
What do you think?
In the sun,
aerobics with an empty stomach.
Good.
Let's go.
Yixing is going all out.
He is working too hard.
It's too hot today.
Let's go.
I'm impressed.
I admire him.
Do you admire him?
Me too.
I've never seen anyone
who loves music as much as Yixing.
Yes.
I have been surrounded by musicians.
I've never seen anyone like him.
He just can't stop.
He loves music so much.
He is so into it.
Too into it.
I think
it's a great merit.
Yes.
It smells so good.
Very nice.
Brown sugar and cinnamon.
I will add some icing too.
Then it will become a filling.
Okay.
Keep going!
Amazing.
It smells good.
Icing.
They look great.
They look great after applying icing.
What are these?
Cinnamon rolls.
Well,
having one of these,
five minutes of my exercise will go into waste.
Really?
Yes.
Go into waste.
Yixing thinks that his exercise
will go into waste.
But you need to have something.
You have to eat something.
You can eat some carbohydrate.
[Put on Weight Very Easily]
But you look good.
I have a concert coming up.
Got it.
We made you the egg and ham.
And some porridge.
Coming.
Oh my...
Well,
that's too much.
All the exercise will go into waste now.
Well,
these rolls,
these rolls
are very filling.
It's very filling.
Let's have the breakfast.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Come on.
Thank you, Mr. Huang.
The cinnamon rolls
look delicious.
Sis.
Here, Mr. He.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. He.
Here is some for you.
Zhang Yixing, taste some.
Okay.
Try one.
It's delicious with milk.
Try some.
Take a bite.
You can eat it if you like it.
It looks delicious.
It's not big. You can share it with Peng.
Peng, you can share it with Yixing.
You two can share one.
No problem.
No problem at all.
Okay.
It looks so good.
What is it called again?
It's my favorite.
Cinnamon rolls.
Right?
It is a pity for meal without carbohydrate.
There is no fun in life.
Carbohydrate is the source
of happiness.
Dopamine.
Have some.
The core bit.
The core bit is the best.
And the sauce.
Try the sauce.
I will have another one.
Peng, have another one.
I am good.
Later.
I can share with Yixing.
What I mean is that
Yixing eats his own one.
Carbohydrate is good for you.
You can have some.
It's good for you.
You need carbohydrate
or it's bad for you.
You have almost finished the whole one.
Finish it.
One more bite.
Eat it.
Have another one.
Have some more.
It's just one more bite.
One more bite.
I'm good.
What am I going to do now?
I had two.
It's delicious.
He wants to have some but he can't.
Yes.
Eat it if you want.
Just do some more exercise afterwards.
It's not good to surppress the urge.
I really can't, Master.
What kind of show it is...
Let's go.
Let's clean up.
When are we
going fishing?
Let's go.
Okay, done.
Let me help you.
I'm on.
I'm coming.
Come on.
You need to push us.
I'm pushing.
Is Peng on the boat?
Let's go.
We are leaving.
Are you on the boat?
Yes.
Good.
Wait, don't move.
Do you think
that the fish will jump up when hearing music?
Stop daydreaming.
Be careful, Peng.
That's it anyway.
Wait, the rope needs tightening up.
You're gonna float away.
Pull him back.
It's okay.
Go lay down.
I'm gonna tie it to my foot.
Tie it to the foot.
Right, this should work.
Today it is really sunny.
Today we speak with sincerity.
Great.
I wish you will catch a big fish.
Catch a big fish.
Mr. Li.
Can you sing it in Cantonese?
Catch a big fish.
Can you try it?
Mr. Li catches a big fish.
Catch a big fish.
I smell the sea.
Yes.
Have you ever joined Live Our Life?
No.
Have you?
I've been here for Season Two and Season Four.
Season Two and Season Four.
I haven't been here once.
So what did you do here before?
No one in Live Our Life
will ask you to do anything here.
Okay.
Just do it if you want to.
I want to work.
I want to cook.
But generally it is Mr. Huang Lei
who cooks, am I right?
You could
help him.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Here we are.
Mr. Zhang Shaogang.
Where's your stuff?
You only take these?
What do you bring?
Yeah, just a luggage
and a bag. That's enough.
Oh, no!
I forgot to take the sausages.
I put it in the hotel's fridge.
That's okay. Let them bring it here then.
Okay.
Who are they?
What are they playing on the sea?
Is their current welcome ceremony
too exaggerated, isn't it?
Mr. Zhang Shaogang!
We're fishing.
Is that Li Ronghao?
Really?
Li Ronghao.
The one with the guitar
should be Li Ronghao, right?
Is that man like Li Ronghao?
Hello.
Sis.
It's not a good time.
They are fishing.
Is that man Li Ronghao?
The one in the middle.
Yes.
Li Ronghao.
Yixing, my bro
and Mr. Li Ronghao
go fishing there.
The one doing nothing in the back
is Peng, right?
That's right.
I guessed right.
Let's get in first.
Let's go.
It's fine.
No, Zifeng.
Now people in Mushroom Cottage
have reached the point
when they have fun
and don't care about people who come here.
No, no.
Where are the two gentlemen?
They are…
Sleeping?
Sleeping.
We are on a lunch break.
Welcome.
It is H.
It is…
H.
Hi, Gong Jun!
Hi, Mr. Zhang Shaogang!
Hi, Wong Cho lam!
Mr. He.
Welcome back.
Finally.
I'm so sorry
for disturbing your rest.
Mr. Huang, I am Gong Jun.
Hello.
Mr. Huang.
Hello, Mr. Huang.
I am Wong Cho lam.
Welcome, Wang Cho lam.
Did you sleep well?
Very well.
Why did you come
when we were taking a nap?
I don't know.
After two years, still no one welcomes me.
I forgot to lock the door.
Well, you even want to lock me out.
This is what Wong Cho lam brings.
Wong Cho lam brings it?
Cho lam, you bring it?
It is so large.
Yes.
Thank you.
I love it very much.
Put it on the coach.
Love it very much.
So considerate.
And there is a small one.
Thank you.
And this,
your good friend,
Miss Color.
And...
See?
Amazing!
A full set.
You're so considerate.
Well,
Sis,
Miss Color looks so disgusting.
This one is so cute.
Are the gifts prepared by the three of us okay?
Are there any more gifts?
Incense.
It smells great.
One for each of you five.
Thank you.
You are so nice.
I bring sausages and pickles made by my grandma.
Let others bring them for you.
I've asked them to bring them.
Five people.
All together?
Yeah.
All together.
And...
And what else?
Books.
You bring books, right?
Laowu.
Because I think it's so good
that if you read it,
you'd love to turn it into a drama.
I think, you and Mr. He,
you two will feel very differently.
That's about us.
Okay.
Again.
Take a look.
O is so pretty.
It's smiling.
Smiling. Comfortable, right?
Massage.
It licks for so long.
That's enough. Really.
Simp.
The dog licks the dog.
O looks like...
Is it pleased or annoyed?
No.
Kind of annoyed.
This dog is so funny.
Look at this pose.
Forget it. I can't watch anymore.
Would you like some coffee, iced coffee?
Sure.
Iced coffee.
Thank you, Mr. He.
Here you are, Wong Cho lam.
Just this morning Li Ronghao said
he had worked with you on music shows.
Yes.
He should have left today.
But he will probably not leave today.
It's up to him.
Great.
Let him stay here.
I like his songs very much.
You like Li Ronghao's songs, don't you?
Yes. Yesterday I heard
Mr. Li Ronghao was here
and I was very happy.
Let your bro
pick up Gong Jun, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
I am very happy.
Don't take this.
Don't take it.
Kind of bothering you.
Don't take a cup of coffee
when seeing your idol.
Am I right?
Yeah.
We can listen to Li Ronghao singing on the spot.
Great.
I can sing too.
We sang If I Were Young last time.
Yes, both of us.
Gong Jun wants to see Li Ronghao.
Peng, send a boat here
to pick up Gong Jun.
Okay.
He failed in the end.
Get up.
Peng, look at your muscles.
Gong Jun, you go by yourself first.
Go on my own?
You can.
Okay, I'll go on my own.
Go on my own.
Mr. Li Ronghao.
I'll send him to you.
Okay.
Come here.
See you later.
Mr. Li Ronghao.
Get on it.
I am here.
He is very happy.
He likes Li Ronghao so much.
Come on.
Okay.
Hello.
I know you.
We met each other last time.
Yeah, we've met before.
That event.
During that event.
Yeah, during the event.
Yes.
Hello, Gong Jun.
Mr. Li Ronghao.
I am very happy.
Finally see you.
Very glad to see you.
I was so happy to know
that you were here yesterday.
Really?
I was going to go today,
but I heard that you were coming.
I shouldn't leave.
Have a rest.
Bro, you are going to release a new song today,
am I right?
Yeah. Used to Stay up Late.
You really follow it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
A happy song.
A very happy one.
I've listened to a little bit.
Yeah, there's a preview today.
Bro, do you know
which of your songs I like the most?
Which one?
Ballad.
I like it too.
Is that about your real experience?
That's the mood to work in a big city
from a small place.
That has resonance for me.
Thank you!
Good.
Slow down.
Thank you!
Cho lam.
It's been a long time.
Have a seat.
We can listen to Li Ronghao singing on the spot.
Play it.
It suddenly turns into a talent show.
So embarrassed.
Play it.
Have you heard Hanjin Tan's songs?
Yes.
I knew him
because of Crime and Punishment (Acoustic).
Crime and Punishment (Acoustic).
The song he wrote for Eason Chan.
♪From eyebrows kept apart♪
♪again it gnaws my heart♪
Have you listened to it?
♪Eat everything up and empty all♪
Very good.
Actually, I'm a little obsessed with this song.
Feel very happy when listening to it.
Could you teach me to play that?
That one.
Oh, this one.
Okay.
See.
Right?
Am I right?
I don't need to make a sound here.
No.
But you have to...
But I need to make a sound here, right?
That was right.
Play it again.
You were right.
Then...
A little fast.
Don't make a sound here.
Should I move?
It's okay.
Let's switch places.
Create obstacles for me,
or I will teach him for a long time.
Mr. Wong Cho lam.
There's an obstacle. We'll...
Mr. Wong Cho lam is sitting uncomfortably.
That's enough.
Otherwise, I'll teach him for two hours.
You don't know him.
Once he touches the guitar,
he won't let you go.
You mentioned the song
of Crime and Punishment (Acoustic).
And you also know Hanjin Tan
and that Eason Chan's song.
I'm happy.
So HK music really...
I grew up listening to HK music
and watching HK films.
I may not watch TVB dramas
less than you.
Really?
I was watching Life on the Line.
Seriously?
No.
I am so happy.
Line Walker. I can get it.
But Life on the Line, really?
The Dripping Sauce.
I've watched it five or six times.
You know it?
The one about selling soy sauce.
I know.
Right, about selling soy sauce.
The latest one called...
dynasty.
Julian Cheung and...
Modern Dynasty.
You...
I...
You are welcome to TVB.
You are welcome to TVB, really.
So when I was watching King of Comedy...
You know, it's different.
Yeah, it has that feeling.
You just want that feeling.
Mr. Li Ronghao has a song
about heroes in Hong Kong.
Which one?
Heroes.
Right, I released a song last year,
called Free Soul.
Yes, Free Soul.
Chow Yun fat, Leslie Cheung...
Yes.
And Kent Cheng.
And that man...
Kent Cheng.
That...
Fei Mao.
I was impressed.
I watched his dramas when I was a boy.
Yes.
You have really watched them all.
I am not kidding you.
Not.
No.
Definitely not kidding you.
You're not only a real fan.
Yes.
He is a "mom fan".
I'm telling you.
Only those moms like my mom
downloaded Modern Dynasty,
and then wait and watch...
They watch sitcoms.
You're such a "mom fan".
You...
I have a particular feeling.
I am most surprised to find on this journey
that you're really...
Let me see if there's anything to drink.
Am I playing right?
Come on.
No.
Play it like this first.
Shall I go back and get some over?
You paddle and I'll go with you.
Okay.
I'll go back and get it for you.
Just flick it here.
Right.
Right, that feeling is right.
Yes.
Let's go. Let's go back.
Let's go.
Let's go back.
It feels good to take a sun bath.
Fish in the waves.
Only waves. No fish.
We didn't even
catch a single one.
You got kind of burnt.
Really?
Kind of.
Here you are.
The aloe gel.
Apply some.
Well, Mr. Zhang.
It won't hurt if you stop rubbing.
Mr. Zhang...
Or you can rub some salt on it.
It's granular.
Okay.
Can I have some on the other arm too?
While
this arm is recovered,
the other one still got burnt.
I'm sorry.
That's it.
Be careful.
I know.
When I was helping you,
did I look like
I was on purpose?
Well.
I'm sure you were on purpose.
Mr. He.
When we were on the boat this noon,
I was practicing the guitar,
and Ronghao and Cho Lam were having fun
talking about Hong Kong TV series.
I was thinking
about joining them.
Seriously?
I wanted to say sorry.
But I didn't know what to do,
because I know nothing about HK series.
In Hong Kong movies,
he is always the villain in Hong Kong movies.
I think it's not a problem
whether you had ignored others
when you were absorbed,
right?
You can't join them on the topic.
And if you try too hard,
you may disrupt them.
I don't know.
It's true.
But I felt that
there was no communication
between us.
Communication is not something
you have to try hard to get.
You've stayed there together for so long.
If it was embarrassing,
you could have returned earlier.
But
they got burnt like that.
Look at his arms.
It proves that you had a good time,
right?
Because you could have returned at any time.
But I think that
if you feel like
you need to communicate,
here's what you can do.
There are
walkie-talkies on the raft, right?
Or you can just play your guitar
or call us to bring you guys
some water or sunscreen.
Just take care of them.
I think it may be because
your interests are too concentrated.
The range is a bit small.
Right?
If you can
have small talks with others
about everything,
you won't have such problems.
But if you
rarely watch HK series
or you know nothing about it,
it would be embarrassing to talk with them.
You don't need to.
I know nothing about it.
Right?
It's just because
you are not good at their topic
today.
I don't think that you
ignored them
when you were playing the guitar.
You didn't.
Let me help you, Mr. Huang.
Sure.
I'll assist you.
You are from Chengdu, right?
Gong Jun.
Yeah. I grew up in Chengdu
and went to college in Shanghai.
Chengdu.
Do you pronounce "I"
as
"Wo"?
It would use your nasal cavity.
"Wo"...
I can't pronounce it.
I was often corrected
when I was filming a movie.
You've been in Chengdu for filming?
I had to speak the Chengdu dialect in
My Sister.
Yeah.
I can't pronounce it.
"Wo"...
They say "Pa'erduo" in the Chengdu dialect.
"Pa'erduo".
Do you know what "Pa'erduo" means?
No.
It means
the wife has the final say.
"Pa'erduo".
The wife holds the purse strings
and has the final say.
Do you cook yourself?
I can cook.
I learned two recipes
of Sichuan cuisine from my dad before coming here.
You should run your words together.
I thought you have two specials.
It turns out that you just learned them.
Well.
I can cook.
You can?
Okay.
I can make a spicy bean sauce fish.
Have you ever tried that before?
And ginger fried spicy chicken.
Sichuan cuisine.
They are tasty.
It sounds amazing.
Nothing.
It's not too difficult.
I'll prepare the ingredients first.
Then I won't get messy.
Let me smash it.
Peel the ginger.
Okay.
Are you going to open a restaurant?
So generous.
You can see that Jun is meant to be a chef.
Where did we get the Sichuan pickles?
It was made
by my grandma.
You brought them here?
Homemade.
Sichuan spicy oil.
I'll have a try tonight.
Are they sausages?
Yeah.
It was made by my dad.
I brought some.
You brought all of them.
You are not here for a meal.
It's like we were invited to your house.
Yeah.
We can play for a little bit.
It's just about 4 now.
It's too early to cook.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's have some tea first.
Have a break, Jun.
I shall prepare the ingredients first.
I was drinking iced coffee this morning.
After Mr. Zhang arrived,
all of us turned to drink hot tea.
Right.
Jasmine tea.
Since he has sat there,
I don't want to remind him that
the paint is still wet.
Yeah. You.
Really?
It was painted by Yixing and Ronghao yesterday.
It was black yesterday.
It was black.
The color of the wood.
And the house was white.
Now it's pink.
It became pinky.
Was it painted by the two of them too?
It was painted by the two of them
and Peng.
You painted a house yesterday?
Everyone together.
Together with Yixing,
I reviewed what we did
yesterday before we slept.
Do you know how much we have done?
We even forgot that we have painted the house.
See?
What have you done?
So many things.
We went to the tree house first.
Drinking coffee.
Talking about music.
Chatting.
Yeah.
And we went back to paint the house.
And we
dug a swimming pool.
Yeah. The swimming pool.
You can see a table up there.
It was a DJ table yesterday.
Yixing, Ronghao, and Sis were playing DJs.
And the crew started
a dance battle with Peng down here.
The friction on the ground
almost caused sparks.
I was like B-boy yesterday.
And last night in the living room,
each of us did about 200 push-ups.
I want to
ask Zhang Yixing and Li Ronghao.
Were you insane yesterday?
I think I would still be crazy
until I leave
here.
Look how I have burnt myself.
Really crazy.
So, you can relax.
You mean that it is enough
for the show...
Yeah.
Even if I did nothing.
Yes.
That is to say, even if I have done a lot,
I could be cut out.
Yes.
The extra things.
You can choose.
I'll go skydiving with you tomorrow morning.
When you go skydiving later,
you should coordinate with your coach
to finish two easy moves.
First, when you exit and during free fall,
hold the straps tightly
and lean on the coach behind you firmly.
Lift your lower legs
with your feet pointing to the top.
Okay?
Okay.
Thank you for
taking me to new heights.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Thank you, coach.
Good luck with our challenge.
Go for it.
I'll go skydiving with you tomorrow morning.
It is moving.
He's trying so hard.
Well, Mr. Zhang.
Don't think that way.
Well,
sometimes,
people fight for dignity.
Dignity, right?
I just need a one-second scene
after skydiving.
Well.
You can land on the ground
beside our tent.
And change the scene.
Like you are a transition.
So I can jump during the day
and land at night,
floating in the sky for a whole day.
Yes.
I see, Mr. Zhang.
You can sing a song here.
We can prepare for you.
You can do karaoke.
And I'll have Yixing drop a beat for you.
You can...
Rolling on the ground.
Then, you can do 200 push-ups in there.
Plus skydiving tomorrow,
you'll get enough
scenes in the show.
You'll be in the post-credit scene.
Well,
Mr. He.
I wipe myself out
only to be in the post-credit scene.
I don't deserve the main feature.
I wipe myself out
just...
No.
Here's the thing.
We'll add one line
after all the credits:
"Don't forget him."
And then we'll show
all your scenes real quick.
In 30 seconds.
It's impossible.
35 seconds.
Mr. He.
Why won't you invite us to go and visit
the tree house today?
Now?
Well.
That would look like a request.
It's okay.
Here's the thing.
Li Ronghao was the only guest back then.
So, it was easier to guide him.
But the three of you
are scattered.
It's difficult.
When can you gather in a group?
We have
a pretty tree house there.
I've been thinking to guide you there.
But you don't gather.
We don't gather?
Really.
Cho Lam was confused
when he came out.
Cho Lam,
if there's anything we haven't played...
We shall do it.
It's all our fault.
Our fault.
We just care about the meal.
Yes.
Well,
can you take Mr. Zhang
for a ride in our car?
Sure.
I think he's also one of our guests.
You can
downsize the activities we made
for Li Ronghao
when you arrange for Mr. Zhang.
Okay?
Let's go for a ride.
Okay.
Okay?
What do you think?
We have a lovely car.
And shut up after this,
okay?
I mean...
No.
That's what you were thinking.
When you finish this,
I'll try my best to satisfy you.
Okay?
Mr. He, do you know
what it has turned to?
What?
Li Ronghao can do it,
why can't I?
Can you scratch the wall
so that I can paint it again?
It's okay.
We can paint it twice.
The color would swell.
Would you like it?
I can arrange it for you.
Really.
Our car is lovely.
Which car?
That one.
This one?
Yes.
Where should I sit?
You can
choose whatever you want.
I'll ride yours.
Sure.
Yes.
Like this?
Yeah.
I'll push the pedal.
Don't be afraid.
Okay.
Mr. Li.
Let's go.
Slow down.
Are you okay with it, Mr. Zhang?
Yeah.
Sure?
Mr. Zhang.
Show that you enjoy it.
Control your face.
Manage it.
Feel the happiness, right?
The haircut looks great.
It's like a carrot.
That's exciting.
To experience...
I'll push it.
Yes, please.
Go.
Okay.
That's it.
Nice.
It's good.
Their wheels are bigger.
Yes.
It's not shaking.
But...
Just a second.
We are...
We are so slow.
What?
Tell you what...
Tell you what,
you can feel like sitting
on a sedan chair.
It goes up and down.
Ours is okay.
It's not.
See? It's not...
Like riding a horse.
I've chosen the right one.
This car is better.
Look.
His car can go anywhere.
This one can't.
Their wheels are wider.
Ready to go to the sea.
It can be in the water.
This is fun.
We can
drive just along the sea.
Let's have a try.
Look.
Mr. Zhang.
Is it exciting?
Very well.
It feels good now.
It feels good when the ground is flat.
Let's drive around the coastline.
You got wet.
Are you okay?
You too.
Well.
I just got there.
Let me find a flat place to
go back there.
It'll be better to have a slope.
Let's go.
It feels bad on the beach.
It's bumping again.
I'll push it.
Let's do it together.
No, I can do it.
You need to push the pedal.
Okay.
Go.
Are you okay with it, Mr. Zhang?
No problem.
Sure.
Is it okay on the flat ground?
No.
You have to go down here.
The angle is small.
I have already...
It's okay.
Come on.
Don't push the pedal.
Let me do it.
Here.
Let's lift it together.
It got stuck.
It...
Come on. Three, two, one.
It should be good.
Come on.
I won't get in it.
I'll just push it here.
No.
Let's move it towards here.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Again. Three, two, one, go.
And I still have to push it.
There's a slope.
I have to push it there.
You can get in.
Let it bump.
Yeah. Just bump.
It's not a big problem.
No.
No. Li Ronghao.
I'll push it toward the grass.
To the grass.
It got stuck.
Go.
It would be better on the grass.
Where do you park it?
You get in and drive it.
The two of us would be too heavy.
There is a vine.
[The unbearable heaviness.]
Let's lift it out of the sand.
No, Mr. Zhang.
I think something's wrong.
No.
Yes.
Well.
Why do we have to do this
while they are having great fun there?
The breeze feels so good.
Okay.
It's out.
Great.
One. Go.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
No.
Why do we have to do this
while they are having great fun there?
I think
something has gone wrong.
Other things were good.
Three, two, one, go.
Three, two, one.
That's it.
You can drive now.
But be sure to avoid the pine trees.
No.
Don't even think about driving it.
I have lost
confidence in this car,
Mr. Zhang.
It can go nowhere,
I think so.
Let me make it right first.
Tell you what,
I'll not get in it.
I'll go on foot...
Cheer for me.
I'll shout out
when something's wrong.
Okay.
Because we are too heavy for it.
We were supposed to go for a drive.
Now we are here to fix the car.
I hate you, Li Ronghao.
You don't need to hate me.
I went for the drive because
I was envious of the activities
you had yesterday.
But we've stolen so many scenes.
They won't have so many scenes.
Let's go.
There's a pit.
Yes.
It's okay here.
Watch out.
I saw that you have spent
a long time rescuing the car.
It fell into a pit.
It got stuck.
It's obvious.
Your hair's messy.
It's so funny.
Hold your hair.
It's all over you,
Mr. Zhang.
You need a shower.
You have to take a shower again.
Which pit did you fall into?
Three to four pits.
Did you fall into them?
Let's skip the details.
Well,
I don't think it's necessary.
Go wash your face.
It's all over your face.
Peng,
just go and ride it
around.
I wonder whether it was the problem with the car,
or the two of us.
Let Gong Jun go for a drive
and see if there's a problem
with the car or with him.
Well.
There should be a passenger.
Because both of us were in the car.
Both of us.
Let me have a try.
Okay. Go.
Go.
Yeah.
It's good.
Okay.
Go.
Just go and see.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Nice.
Drive toward the sea.
People would like to drive toward the sea.
Yeah.
They are cool now.
They'll feel even cooler near the sea.
Only if it touches the water.
Yes.
It's smooth here.
No.
Just go straight.
Say a word for them.
Waverider.
Mr. He.
What?
Was Li Ronghao
happy when he was in the car?
Yes, he was.
Aren't you happy with it after getting
what you want?
Mr. He.
Look at me.
Why are you in a mess?
Why is there sand all over you?
And
even on your shoulders and hair.
Why?
Because when we got stuck in a sand pit,
I was there pushing the car.
When a wheel is stuck in a pit
and the driver keeps pushing the gas pedal,
the sand thrown up
just covered me.
We didn't ride it back,
Mr. He.
It wasn't like that.
We pushed it back.
Why is this happening to you?
I don't know.
They're back.
It runs well.
Nothing happened, Mr. Zhang.
Nothing.
It feels great.
It was the first time
that I saw someone has sand on his face.
Well, Mr. He.
What do you mean?
What I mean is that
someone must have done something wrong.
But you were not the driver,
right?
Yes.
It was Li Ronghao, right?
So, he must have done something wrong.
It's his problem, right?
It must be his problem.
It has nothing to do with us.
I passed the buck
to our guest.
It's rare that all of us are here.
Let's take a photo together.
Sure.
Mr. Zhang, you can sit there,
for you were just covered with sand.
Sure.
Come on.
Gong Jun.
Where's Ronghao?
Let's take one first.
He's the guest of the last episode.
Let's take one first
and get him then.
He is the guest of the last episode.
Yes, indeed.
I've heard all of it.
Were you talking about me?
My eyelid suddenly twitched.
I must have been mentioned.
I have to come out.
I can't miss
anything good.
Three, two, one.
Time to cook.
It doesn't feel right.
I don't feel right.
I feel sick.
[What happened to Mr. Huang?]
[A few hours ago...]
My head aches. It feels like a heatstroke.
I think I'm having a little heatstroke.
I should drink some Zhengqi Liquid later.
I'll get you some.
My head is spinning.
Give me two doses.
Okay.
Thank you.
I feel dizzy.
Maybe it's because
I slept with the air conditioning.
And you went out in a hurry.
You were in a hurry when they arrived.
I feel dizzy. I need to lie down for a bit.
I can't deal with it.
I have to arrange the things.
Yixing.
Master.
I feel kind of unwell.
Heatstroke?
I don't know.
You'll need to cook.
No problem.
I'll cook whatever you say.
Jiong,
I have to go and vomit.
What's wrong?
I need to lie down a bit.
I feel unwell.
Go and take a break.
I'll tell you what to do.
I'll cook.
Listen to me.
Tell me.
Help me
cut the chicken into small...
Small cubes, I get it.
Small cubes.
Okay?
Okay.
I can do it.
Yixing, you cook the ribs
in the bigger basin.
And the smaller one is for Cho Lam to cook
Steamed Pork Ribs in Black Bean Sauce.
Okay?
Okay.
You don't need to cook today.
Let Mr. Huang have a rest tonight.
We'll do
whatever we can.
Just take a rest, Huang.
Go and lie down for a bit.
I'll lie down for a minute.
He feels unwell today.
He has drunk two doses of Zhengqi Liquid.
Here?
37.3.
A mild fever.
A low-grade fever.
I feel unwell.
Take a good rest.
Do I have to turn off the AC?
No.
It's okay.
Tell them what to do.
I'll cook later.
Don't worry about it.
We can do it.
It's difficult to cut
the chicken into small cubes.
I have to chop it up.
Can you do it?
Where do I start from?
I'll do it.
You can pull these parts off.
Then they can be complete.
Be careful with your hand.
It's okay.
The posture seems...
Take your time.
We can let Gong Jun do it.
Let me do it.
Here.
I'll pull it off.
Are you looking up the recipe?
Do you have to follow the recipe?
Yes.
Because I never
cooked clay pot rice.
But I can do it.
Are you sure you want to cook clay pot rice?
It's great.
I haven't eaten it for ages.
Use that?
Ribs.
Sure.
Clay pot rice with pork ribs.
It will be OK.
I won't fail.
Even if it's the first time, everyone can...
Succeed?
Succeed.
Okay. I'll count on you.
I think it's okay now.
Let me fry the fish.
[Cooking spicy bean sauce fish]
The pot is too small.
Hold it.
Use it.
Turn.
From here.
Yeah.
That's it.
Just fry it like this.
It's okay.
Leave it open.
Flip it.
Fry the other side later.
Just fry this side first.
Yes.
Call me if you need help.
I can do it. Fry it until it is golden.
[The tail is still raw.]
What do I do?
Is it too hot?
Let me help you.
I'll wear a glove
to help you take off the head.
Lift it.
Don't burn yourself.
Okay. Don't move it.
Okay.
Okay. Great.
[The head fell off.]
It's okay.
Let me take it away.
Fish heads are kind of old-fashioned.
Nobody eats fish heads.
I'll do it.
I can assemble it
in the dish
later.
Oh! My fish.
What's wrong?
It fell apart.
Oh! My fish.
Did it get loose?
It didn't.
It's okay. It's not necessary
to be in complete form.
Yeah.
Right?
Let me help you.
I'll try my best.
I'll pour it.
It's already there.
It's okay.
My fish.
Look at it.
What can I do?
Oh! My fish.
Let me help you.
Look, Jun.
Who knows that the fish was loose?
Right?
Put it back.
It's complete again.
Really.
It looks great.
What is it?
Mr. Huang got up.
Mr. Huang.
Feeling better?
I'm good.
I don't know.
It hurts here.
Do you need any medicine?
Is it because of the squid?
Was it totally roasted?
Not really.
What about the dishes?
Have you prepared everything?
I'm afraid that,
when he saw what we've done,
he would feel worse.
Prepare some squid.
Squid again?
You haven't dealt with the chicken, right?
I am afraid of it.
I'll do it.
Cut some Thai pepper.
Let Jun cut some.
He's good at it.
And prepare some
green garlic,
Cho Lam. It's in the green box.
And Jun, help me cut the tofu
into cubes.
Small cubes. It's for Mapo Tofu.
Okay.
Jiong, can you help me wash the pot?
Sure.
Let me fry the chicken.
Nice.
Sis,
can you help Jun put the sausage on a dish
and put them in the steam box?
Sure.
Take a rest, Huang.
Okay.
I think it'll be better
if we can put them in two dishes.
And we have so many people here.
We can put one on each side of the table.
Yeah. Get a small plate.
Let me wash them.
Spatula, right?
I'll wash it for you.
Thank you, Mr. He.
Here, Mr. Zhang.
I have to wash it right away.
Yeah.
Yixing needs it now.
Here you are, Yixing.
[Garlic pork ribs]
[Yixing's special.]
[Chicken stew with ginger juice]
[Cooked by Gong Jun]
You've finished it, right?
Yes, it's done.
Is everything okay?
Are you doing good with the dishes?
Quite good.
What are you going to cook?
Scrambled eggs with green peppers.
Just scrambled green peppers?
With scrambled eggs.
I'll start.
As soon as I start to cook,
I begin to fumble.
Such a mess.
Master, be careful.
It's okay. I'm good.
Wait. The oil isn't hot enough.
If you add it now, it will stick to the pan.
Hot enough. Look, it's bubbling.
It's bubbling.
But no smoke yet.
There is still no smoke.
I just want to cook scrambled eggs this way.
I'm doing good!
Are you done, Peng?
Not yet.
It's ready to be served, isn't it?
It can be ready.
Almost.
It will be ready.
[Peng's scrambled eggs with green peppers]
Done.
It's ready.
It can be served.
So all your hope now is it can be served...
I promise.
Let's enjoy dinner.
[Hong Kong-style rice casserole]
[Cooked by Wong Cho Lam]
[Chicken stew with ginger juice]
[Cooked by Gong Jun]
[Fish stew with bean paste]
[Homemade sausage]
[Cooked by Gong Jun]
[Scrambled eggs with green peppers]
[Cooked by Peng Yuchang]
[Spicy diced chicken]
[Cooked by Huang Lei]
[Stir-fried Doufu in hot sauce]
[Spare ribs with garlic sauce]
[Cooked by Zhang Yixing]
Look at all these dishes. Wonderful!
They smell good.
Okay.
Thank you, guys.
Come here.
Thank you all.
Thank you.
Welcome, everyone.
Let's have the dinner.
Don't feel shy.
I'll try the chicken Gong Jun cooked first,
because I saw him cooking it.
Gong Jun!
Bravo!
Thank you.
Yixing, the spare ribs you cooked taste very good.
I have learned from Master.
Yixing specializes in it.
We call him Spare Ribs Zhang.
I'll get more.
The dish Peng cooked also tastes good.
It's delicious.
It's nice.
The scrambled eggs with green peppers
is really good.
I'll get some rice.
The scrambled eggs with green peppers
will go well with the rice.
Three more minutes.
Let's just wait.
The rice below is ready.
Let's flip it.
Why do the scrambled eggs taste so good?
Cho Lam, the rice isn't ready yet.
But I just can't wait for three more minutes.
The scrambled eggs with green peppers are so good.
Peng, believe me,
Cho Lam is eating this dish all the time.
Really?
He's doing this not because
he hopes to help you prove yourself.
Definitely not.
He just loves it.
I'm glad you like it.
Somebody's smiling secretly
with his hand covering his mouth.
Thank you, Cho Lam.
Cheers.
I really think it's nice.
I guess it's time
Peng gained a good name for cooking.
Yes.
I must take my scrambled eggs with green peppers
to directors.
They gotta have a taste.
Spare some of the food.
Right, I can spare some.
I gotta win a round today.
Definitely.
I must hear their cheers.
They'll cheer for sure.
Have a taste first!
Cheering without tasting just hurts me.
Give it a shot.
It's delicious.
Right?
You shall cheer when I walk back, okay?
Okay.
When I reach the...
Don't cheer until I'm about to sit down,
okay?
Get ready.
The cheers are amazing.
Right. They should be.
We can hear.
Now I've restored my reputation for cooking.
The pickles! We forgot them.
Yes! I was also thinking about it.
Yes. The pickles.
I'll get some.
Only one bag.
One bag is enough.
The other one is for tomorrow's breakfast.
The pickles.
Some for you guys.
Thank you.
The pickles.
And some for you guys.
Many thanks, Gong Jun.
My grandma made the chili sauce.
Many thanks to your grandma.
Yummy.
My grandma is good at making yummy pickles.
It tastes so good.
Mr. Gong, could you do me a favor?
May I have some more pickles?
Then we've got nothing for tomorrow.
One bag is left.
For tomorrow's breakfast,
the pickles must be appetizing.
Porridge with pickles, right?
I'll just tell you my home address.
Mr. Zhang, I'll charge.
Do you know how lovely he is?
During the Spring Festival,
He sent me Chinese liquor again.
I asked him why he did this
and if he thought I was a good drinker.
He replied that
when sending greetings,
the young should send liquor to the old man.
You said Mr. Zhang is one of the old man?
No.
I didn't say the old man.
I said the senior.
The senior?
That's correct.
Mr. He,
has Gong Jun ever sent you
60% Chinese liquor?
No.
That proves that
you are still young.
I'm not young,
but I'm not a senior yet, either.
Chinese liquor.
Gong Jun only sent it
to the old man.
Gong Jun keeps saying beside me...
It should be the senior.
He's trying to correct it.
Yes.
Is there anything we'll do tonight?
Karaoke.
But you said you'd go to bed, right?
It's okay.
Won't the noise bother you?
Not at all.
Noise is nothing to me.
Just enjoy yourselves.
Don't worry about the volume.
I'm happy to listen to you sing.
I'll go in and cool myself off.
Take a rest, Mr. Huang.
Go on with your dinner.
Sure.
Have a rest.
He gotta have a rest.
I tell you that
he'll get better soon considering his fitness.
He's strong.
He's a man at the top of the food chain.
Cho Lam, you're eating
so intently.
Intently.
Cho Lam is a big carb eater.
Cho lam, you don't limit your carb intake?
I was standing beside Mr. He
in the show every day,
so there's no point limiting my carb intake.
Obviously,
one looks slim,
while the other looks round.
Come on.
You're exaggerating.
Cho Lam, you're really exaggerating.
Just elliptical, maybe?
I'm sorry.
OK, you can be a host.
Does it hurt?
Not that much.
It looks bad,
but
it doesn't hurt that much.
It even turns purple.
Because you stay here for two days,
including yesterday.
We only stay here for half a day,
but you stay here longer.
You should have left today.
But Mr. Zhang Shaogang comes here
and I'm longing to meet you.
Upon hearing the news you'd come,
I said where the directors are.
Could I stay here for another half an episode?
I meant it.
Don't kick me out, okay?
I was clinging to the pillar,
but the camera was off then.
I nearly broke the pillar,
Mr. Zhang.
Li Ronghao, you...
Mr. Li.
Just kidding.
I'm so happy.
We haven't seen each other for a long time.
Yes.
I'm so happy to meet you today.
We're all so happy.
So happy.
Well,
last time I met him,
we seldom
talked.
We didn't talk.
You were quiet.
You were so quiet then.
Yes.
So there's a reason for your sunburn.
You talked heartily.
Yes.
Cho Lam and I kept
talking about TVB dramas.
He knows them better than I do.
Yixing told me today
Cho Lam and Ronghao had a lively talk.
I'm even familiar with extras in TVB dramas.
Seriously?
He asked me if he should join them
instead of just practicing the guitar.
I answered he should check
if he knew something about the topic.
Walking library of TVB dramas.
Kent Cheng is the man nodding all the time?
Yes.
You also watched it, right?
You...
Well,
Yixing tried to join us several times,
but I didn't give him the opportunity.
He failed to join us because of us.
What's its melody?
[Only they can enjoy happiness]
It's true, right?
Yixing said today
he like Hanjin Tan's song,
Crime and Punishment (Acoustic).
And Li Ronghao said
he like TVB dramas.
Every time I hear similar words,
I feel
so moved.
Mr. Huang and I had a chat today.
I said Cho Lam is awesome.
I can't imagine
going to TVB alone
and hosting a show in Cantonese.
Seriously.
It is impossible.
That's not my stage.
Also, it was not...
It was just not proper for me
to make jokes.
So Cho Lam,
you are such a great relief to me.
You are also a great relif to me.
Cheers for Songs Forever.
We had each other.
The show is good.
During
Songs Forever,
George Lam
is just like this.
If Mr. He asked him,
"Do you like the dish,
scrambled eggs with green peppers?"
[I, well]
[I just]
[I, scrambled eggs with green peppers...]
I couldn't even hear what he was saying,
but you could!
Standing aside,
I heard nothing at all.
Neither did I.
Really?
I guessed by the movement of his lips.
I thought you could...
I just watched his lips and guessed.
For example, once he said,
"I've been singing it for decades,
"but I've got a different vibe today."
Mr. He is amazing.
I thought I was the only one
who couldn't hear him clearly.
You also couldn't, right?
I was always standing aside
and trying so hard to listen.
What on earth is he saying?
But the audience heard him clearly.
Because
they were listening to his voice through his mic.
They could listen to speakers.
The audience were listening to speakers.
On the stage.
Got it.
Only Coco talked loudly and clearly.
Actually, I think Coco
could lower her voice a little bit.
Yixing! Long time no see!
Miss you! Everybody!
Hi!
Thank you! I love you!
Thank you all! Thank you!
May I mop the floor?
Thank you!
Maybe Coco could...
[Calm down]
Coco is so cute.
Time for karaoke.
Let's go.
Will you sing If I Were Young?
Sure.
Let's sing it.
Let's go.
I can sing that song.
[Break time]
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
No.
What's going on?
It's out of battery.
We've been playing it for a whole day yesterday.
It's out of battery now.
Do you see how sad Gong Jun looks?
It's fine.
My If I Were Young...
Really...
You should sing it.
We must
arrange this today.
I must sing it.
Let's do it unplugged, okay?
Okay.
Take your phone out.
Find the lyrics first.
No. I don't need them.
You can memorize them?
I can memorize them.
Mr. Li.
Please sing it live for us.
No problem.
[Live Our Life Concert]
[Ft. Li Ronghao]
Which key do you want to sing in?
Do a G major.
Go with a G major.
You can sit here.
Okay!
Let's have Ronghao
lead us with the song.
Okay.
The TV keeps blinking.
Awesome.
Thanks, Yixing.
Thanks, Ronghao.
Thank you.
Amazing.
Thanks for the claps.
One, two, three, four.
♪The TV keeps blinking.♪
♪I haven't deleted your number.♪
♪You treated me well.♪
♪But I ruined it like that.♪
Hold on.
The pitch was off.
It was a little low, right?
You sang in a higher key.
I did?
No.
He just created another song.
I felt something's wrong.
You sang in a higher key.
I did that?
Let's do this. Ronghao, you sing first.
He will follow you.
You go first.
Okay. I'll go first.
Right.
♪The TV keeps blinking.♪
♪I haven't deleted your number.♪
♪You treated me well.♪
That's right.
♪But I ruined it like that.♪
♪We had a common dream.♪
♪A roof over our heads.♪
♪To make ends meet, we worked day and night.♪
♪But we couldn't even afford the down payment♪
♪The wallboard I smashed♪
♪hasn't been repaired yet.♪
Do you know this song?
Yes. But I don't know the lyrics.
And I have myopia.
♪Your eyes are always reddened.♪
♪The way you loved me,♪
♪I didn't realize it at the time.♪
♪If I were young and promising, not inferior,♪
♪if I have tasted regret.♪
♪Money and status,♪
♪I have them now but I want to go back.♪
♪If I were young and promising,
and knew what to do,♪
♪I wouldn't let you suffer for me.♪
♪At the wedding, I had a few more drinks♪
♪with the one you're with now.♪
♪At the wedding, I had a few more drinks.♪
♪Wish me a promising youth.♪
Many years ago,
in 2017, Ronghao...
Right?
I let him sign for me.
Really?
Yeah, I remember.
I wrote a note.
Yes, I remember.
I let my manager to give it to Ronghao.
Yes.
I had so much fun today.
Honestly,
Mr. Zhang was really loud.
He was major in the recording.
Mr. Zhang again.
Because everyone was listening to the song,
Mr. Zhang couldn't find somebody
to disturb you.
He dragged Sis into this.
The reason that I gave you all
the same gift
is that
everyone feels differently.
It's divided in halves.
The first half is you.
I'll go take a look.
Okay.
You've been disturbing, Mr. Zhang.
Mr. Zhang Shaogang.
I think he's very intentional.
He wanted to try his best
to get into the VIP version.
Yes.
I think I made a good decision
to join this episode.
You like competition,
right?
Of course.
Not in many years.
This is better than karaoke.
We like live music.
Live music.
Bravo.
Can we do King of Comedy?
This rhythm!
King of Comedy is great.
♪I look at a kiwi.♪
♪Suddenly I burst into tears.♪
♪I don't really love to make a fuss.♪
♪This is called telepathy.♪
♪If you don't believe me,
you can ask Li Qingzhao.♪
♪I was never someone who loved to show off,♪
♪but I had too many art cells.♪
♪The romances I've had
and dates I've been to may be few.♪
Yixing is great.
♪But the sufferings I've had from shots and stabs♪
♪are too gorgeous to be hidden.♪
♪Why must I lose all the love in this world♪
♪and be a special guest star to all the tragedy?♪
Gong Jun knows all the lyrics.
♪My heart gets broken, and I cry so hard,♪
♪just like in a Hong Kong movie.♪
♪Why must I cry all the tears in the world♪
♪that I endorse for tissues in the market.♪
♪Next to me, you're not pathetic.♪
♪This is a kind of contribution.♪
The next section is...
♪Those got separated...♪
This song is so touching.
I haven't played this song for so many years.
The thing Yixing was doing
was good.
Yixing did that part.
That was so good.
That...
Okay.
Model
is obviously doable, right?
He knows it. Gong Jun's got it again.
Model.
You must know about Model, right?
Model. For sure.
Of course, I know Model.
Gong Jun made a good decision to be here.
It's a fan meeting event to him.
Yes.
Right?
I am so happy.
Yixing,
are you ready?
I'm ready.
Let's start with G chord.
Okay.
♪Standing and wearing beautiful clothes♪
♪to satisfy primitive desires.♪
Three.
♪Use the perfect facial expression♪
♪to hold the vulnerable city.♪
♪What else can I see aside from the light?♪
♪What else can I ask for
aside from the brightness?♪
♪Who else can I rely on aside from you?♪
♪What are you yelling for
from a thousand miles away?♪
♪What will you want to
remember in a hundred years?♪
♪Can I see that moment again before I leave?♪
♪Remember that your eyes will brighten♪
♪and my arms will be waving.♪
♪Who says there're already
no options in the world?♪
♪While I feel pleasure and anger,
and you feel sad and happy,♪
♪let's sing a bit of a love song.♪
♪It's nothing much
but just to prove that we're still alive.♪
It's so great to sing with the original singer.
Don't.
Make a count.
How many songs now?
Remember to pay the check later.
Well.
I felt the atmosphere was nice.
And suddenly it became mundane.
Name a price, Ronghao.
Those wavings earlier won't count.
It was like that.
But then, it was like "name a price".
There's
an accompanist too.
There's that?
No.
That's between us.
Don't bother.
Give him 80.
That's usually the case.
I will just play randomly.
You can keep chatting.
We're just
doing some
background music.
Did you always invite
people like Yixing
who know music here?
It's the first time in this season.
We've had some before.
Like when Lao Lang was here.
Right?
I'll leave soon.
You need to write the diary.
Okay.
I'll do that now.
After that, you all should go to sleep.
Mr. Li.
Come on.
Ronghao,
you'll not sleep here, right?
Yeah. I'm heading back.
Then sign for us.
I know. I'll write the diary.
Diary.
After that,
sing your diary.
And then 50 pushups.
More for me, right?
Do I really need this?
Let me think.
Bye.
Wait.
Goodbye.
You should not send wishes for us.
Write what you got out of the past few days.
You can say it was very full.
That was too full.
Please cut some of me off this episode.
Leave some parts
to Mr. Zhang.
Ronghao,
I'm so happy.
We've got ahead of the next group by a lot.
Well.
Please be careful with Mr. Zhang.
I'm sorry.
Do it again.
I wrote Fu wrong.
How come?
I wrote an extra dot.
It's too full.
Your portion's too full.
Again. Too full.
Ronghao,
do you have to do extra
even when writing the diary?
It's okay.
That's it.
I'm telling you.
It's fine.
I'm impressed.
Right.
Alright. I'll leave for real.
For real.
Okay.
I'll take you out.
I feel so bad.
I'm gonna leave now.
Bye, Mr. He.
Let's go.
He's tanned.
It's like he's here for training.
Very much.
Everyday's full of things.
Yes.
[Guest's Diary]
Very happy.
It was exactly what I was looking for.
In 2022,
I wish I can have an even skin tone
and be my better self.
[Wish we all have something to look forward to.]
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Now we will have
a cucurbit flute duo.
Butterflies By The Ocean.
It's such a mess.
Teach me.
One, two, three, four.
Is this correct?
Yes.
I'll go skydiving soon.
So high!
You got it!
I'll dive with Peng.
Can't wait.
He's good!